Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committees, task torces, and working groups, 1941-1983; MS2012 Series 2; 22.5 Linear feet
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer Staff Report, 1964 March (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Becker Amendment on School Prayer, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Amendments to the Constitution, 1967-1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - General, 1968-1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - Court Cases, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - H.B. 9, Recitation of the Ten Commandments, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): School Prayer - H.B. 119 on Voluntary Recitation of the Lord's Prayer, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): University of Maryland - Observance of Jewish Holidays, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): University of Maryland - Observance of Jewish Holidays, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): University of Maryland - Observance of Jewish Holidays, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): University of Maryland - Observance of Jewish Holidays, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): University of Maryland - Proposed Changes in the Campus Human Relations Code, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Use of Public School Facilities for Religious Purposes - Brandon vs. Board, of Education, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Use of Public University Facilities for Religious Purposes, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Beth Sar Shalom - Christian Mission to the Jews, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Christmas Pageant of Peace, 1954-1956 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Christmas Pageant of Peace, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Christmas Pageant for Peace - US District Court Transcripts, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Christmas Pageant for Peace - US District Court Transcripts, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Creche on Montgomery County Parkland, May, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Gallaudet College - Proselytizing, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Jews for Jesus Evangelicism, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Needs of Employees as they Relate to the Scheduling of Work, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious needs of Employees - Montgomery County Bill 1-79, 1979 January (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Religious Symbols on Public Property, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Proselytizing Incident at Kings Dominion, Virginia, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Stamps - Issuance of Sectarian Postage Stamps, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1954-1957 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1959 January-April (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1959 May-June (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1959 July-October (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1959 November-December (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1960 January-July (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1960 August-December (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1961 January-September (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1961 October-December (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Sunday Blue Laws, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Tax Exemption of Religious Property, 1964-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Unification Church ("Moonies"), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Washington D.C. Tax Exemption Bill, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Washington D.C. Tax Exemption Bill, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Intergroup Relations Committee (IGR): Washington for Jesus Rally, 1980 April 29 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Social Action Conference, 1975 December 14 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - A Social Action Handbook, 1976 March (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Reassessment Committee - The Role of the Jewish Community in Urban Affairs, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Reassessment Committee - The Role of the Jewish Community in Urban Affairs, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Subcommittee on Health and Welfare, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Subcommittee on the District of Columbia, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Caucus of Social Action Chairman of Jewish Organizations (COSAC) - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Caucus of Social Action Chairmen (COSAC) - Workshop on Minority Business Entrepreneurship, 1970 March 26 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Dispute Between Seymour Wolf and Arthur Waskow, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Jewish Urban Special Projects Fund of Greater Washington, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: "Habirah" - JCCGW Community Action Newsletter, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Jewish Social Action Caucus Newsletter, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Jewish Social Action Caucus Newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Abortion Amendment, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Abortion - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Abortion Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Aging - UJA Council on Aging: Draft Reports, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Aging - UJA Council on Aging: Draft Reports, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Aging - UJA Council for the Aging, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Aging - UJA Council for the Aging, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Aging - JCCGW on Support for the Aging, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Elections - Questionnaire for National Candidates in 1976 election, 1976 September (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Elections - Questionnaire for Maryland Candidates, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Elections - Electorial College Reform, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Farm Workers, 1968-1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Foster Home Program - For Love of Children, Inc., 1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Full Employment Legislation, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Full Employment Legislation, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Indochinese Refugees (Boat People), 1979 February-November (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Labor Reform Act, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Lobbying Act of 1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Mayor Barry Task Force for Social Issues, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Mortgage Interest Rates, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Mortgage Interest Rates - Conference on Mortgage Investment Practices, 1974 September 15 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Summer Jobs Program, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Anti-Sex Discriminatory Language Bill, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Coalition of Conscience, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Freedom of Information/Ethnicity Bill, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Home Rule Legislation, 1951-1963 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Home Rule Legislation, 1964-1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Home Rule Legislation, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Home Rule Legislation, 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Home Rule Legislation, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Human Relations Council, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Neighborhood Reinvestment Commission, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Public Colleges, 1958-1966 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Save the City Campaign (Anti-redlining), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Teachers Colleges - Merger of Wilson and Miner Teachers' Colleges, 1950-1952 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Voting Rights Amendment, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Tax Exemption Bill 2-117, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Voting Rights Amendment, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Voting Rights Amendment, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Voting Rights Amendment, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: D.C. Voting Rights Amendment, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Federal City College, 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Free D.C. Movement, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Forum on Civil Rights, 1976 September 09 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: HR 12261 Revision of D.C. Criminal Code, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Mayor Washington's State of the City Address, 1977 March 15 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Reciprocal Income Tax, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Repeal of D.C. Tax on Food and Drugs, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: Title X Draft Proposal to Revise D.C. Property Tax, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Urban Affairs/Social Action: UDC Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Reports, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Reports, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1973 January-March (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1973 April-December (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1974 January-July (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1974 August-December (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry - General Information Booklet, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1975 January-March (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1975 July-September (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1975 October-December (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1976 July-December (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1976 January-June (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1977 January-July (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1977 August-December (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1978 January-February (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1978 March-June (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1978 July-August (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1978 September-December (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1979 January-March (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1979 April-August (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1979 September-December (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry - General, 1980 January-December (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Plight for Soviet Jewry Committee, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Plight of Soviet Jewry Committee, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry - Community Action Programs, 1965-1970 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Sabbath, 1965 March 12-13 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Plight of Soviet Jewry Committee - Mass Protest Meeting, 1965 09 June (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Plight of Soviet Jewry Committee - Mass Protest Meeting, 1965 09 June (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Eternal Light Vigil, 1965 September 19 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Eternal Light Vigil, 1965 September 19 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Eternal Light Vigil, 1965 September 19 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry Demonstration - Lafayette Park, 1966 September 19 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: The Tragedy of Soviet Jewry Exhibition, 1966 October 30 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Presentation of Declaration of Rights of Soviet Jewry, 1966 December 09 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Community Demonstrations for Soviet Jewry, 1966 December 11 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry Rally, 1968 October 13 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: American Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Delegate Assembly on Programming for Soviet Jewry, 1969 June 23 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on Behalf of Boris L. Kochubiyevsky, 1969 July 10-24 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: New Years Greeting Card Project to Soviet Synagogues, 1969 September (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Soviet Jewry Youth Rally, 1969 October 12 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Nehama Lifschitz Concert, 1969 November 16 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Chaining Demonstrations Court Transcript, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visits of Yasha Kasakov and Boris Sperling, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Board of Jewish Education Workshop on Soviet Jewry, 1970 January 18-19 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Moscow Philharmonic Soviet Jewry Demonstration, 1970 January 19 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jewish Liberation Project Soviet Jewry Protest, 1970 January 22 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Boris Kochubiyevsky Drive, 1970 March 25 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Assembly on Soviet Jewry, 1970 April 26 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry Youth Fast for Freedom, 1970 May-August (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Leningrad Hijacking Arrests, 1970 June-August (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: New Years Greeting Card Program to Soviet Synagogues, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Leningrad Hijacking Arrests, 1970 September-October (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Assembly Protesting Imprisonment of Leningrad Jews, 1970 September 21 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Moiseyev Ballet Demonstration, 1970 September 23-24 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Mobilization for Soviet Jewry, 1970 October 11-12 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Mobilization for Soviet Jewry, 1970 October 11-12 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: President's Meeting on Show Trials - Temple Israel, 1970 November 17 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Emergency Meeting: Leningrad Hijacking Show Trial - Washington Cathedral, 1970 November 24 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Leningrad Hijacking Trials, Sentencing, Appeal, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Violent Demonstrations Against Soviet Targets, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Meeting of Seymour Wolf with Soviet Diplomats, 1970 December 29 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Candlelight March Protesting Sentencing at Leningrad Trials, 1970 December 29 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Rusineck and Aisenstadts, 1971 February 03 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Siberian Dancers Demonstration, 1971 February 13-14 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: World Conference on Soviet Jewry - Brussels, 1971 February 23-25 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: World Conference on Soviet Jewry - Brussels, 1971 February 23-25 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: World Conference on Soviet Jewry - Brussels, 1971 February 23-25 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jewish Community Council Meeting with Dobrynin, 1971 March 11 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Cabling Communist Party Leaders in Support of Soviet Jewry, 1971 March (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Clergy Statement to Dobrynin, 1971 March 30 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1971 April 17 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry Day Proclamation in PG County, 1971 April 18 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Week, 1971 May 11-21 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Journal of Soviet Jewish Affairs - "Exodus,", 1971 June (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Prayer Vigil, 1971 June 03 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jewish Identity Week for Soviet Jewry, 1971 June 23-27 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry Seminar, 1971 August 09 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Invitations to 5 Soviet Jews, 1971 September 17 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry - Sylvan Theater and Lincoln Memorial, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry - Publicity, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry - Letters from Congress, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry - Letters from Congress, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Rally for Soviet Jewry - Letters from Congress, 1971 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Soviet Jewish Apologists - D. Dragunsky, et al, 1971 October 20 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Human Rights for Soviet Jewry, 1971 December 06 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry Hotline, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Delegation to Soviet Embassy, 1971 December 15 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - JCCGW "Undercover,", 1971 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Arts and Crafts Exhibit and Osipov Dancers, 1972 January-February (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Ruth Alexandrovich Averbuch, 1972 January 07-09 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Emergency Community Meeting - B'nai Israel Congregation, 1972 March 05 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Petition Campaign for Soviet Jews to President Nixon, 1972 February-May (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Interreligious Consultation on Soviet Jewry, 1972 March-November (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Reception Honoring Boris Kochubiyevsky, 1972 May 15 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Boris (Yankelzon) Azernikov, 1972 May (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Roman Rutman, 1973 May (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Testimony on Soviet Jewry to Young Republicans by Isaac Franck, 1972 July 21 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets of August 12, 1952, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Paulina Korenblit - Emergency Planning Meeting, 1972 August 31 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry Emigration Tax, 1972 August (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry Emigration Tax, 1972 August-November (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Congressional Response to Soviet Jewry Emigration Tax, 1972 August-October (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Mass Demonstration against Soviet Emigration Tax, 1972 September 17 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Unity Day Simhat Torah Rally, 1972 September 30 - October 01 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Demonstration for M.V. Keldysh, 1972 October 18 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewish Artists Boris Penson Exhibit, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)